{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Quick, type anything!**",
            "answer": [""],
            "time": 5,
            "chance": 0.2
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Type this: `bawk`**",
            "answer": ["bawk"],
            "time": 5,
            "chance": 0.05
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Type this: `mr bawk is yes`**",
            "answer": ["mr bawk is yes"],
            "time": 10,
            "chance": 0.05
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Type the alphabet!**",
            "answer": ["abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz"],
            "time": 15,
            "chance": 0.05
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Type the alphabet, with spaces in between!**",
            "answer": ["a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z"],
            "time": 25,
            "chance": 0.05
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **What discord module do I run on?**",
            "answer": ["discord.py", "discordpy"],
            "time": 10,
            "chance": 0.1
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **What is this colour & shape: {EMOJI}? (Respond in <colour> <shape>)**",
            "answer": ["{COLSHAPEANS}"],
            "time": 10,
            "chance": 0.15
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **What is my sister bot?**",
            "answer": ["treble"],
            "time": 5,
            "chance": 0.05
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Complete the sentence: No _! (Hint: Uno)**",
            "answer": ["u", "you"],
            "time": 5,
            "chance": 0.1
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Complete the sentence: Its over ______!**",
            "answer": ["9000", "nine thousand", "9 thousand"],
            "time": 7,
            "chance": 0.1
        },
        {
            "question": ":parrot::video_game: **Complete the sentence: That's a lotta _______**",
            "answer": ["damage"],
            "time": 5,
            "chance": 0.1
        }
    ]
}